GROUP:      certificates.k8s.io
KIND:       CertificateSigningRequest
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    CertificateSigningRequest objects provide a mechanism to obtain x509
    certificates by submitting a certificate signing request, and having it
    asynchronously approved and issued.
    
    Kubelets use this API to obtain:
     1. client certificates to authenticate to kube-apiserver (with the
    "kubernetes.io/kube-apiserver-client-kubelet" signerName).
     2. serving certificates for TLS endpoints kube-apiserver can connect to
    securely (with the "kubernetes.io/kubelet-serving" signerName).
    
    This API can be used to request client certificates to authenticate to
    kube-apiserver (with the "kubernetes.io/kube-apiserver-client" signerName),
    or to obtain certificates from custom non-Kubernetes signers.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    <no description>

  spec	<CertificateSigningRequestSpec> -required-
    spec contains the certificate request, and is immutable after creation. Only
    the request, signerName, expirationSeconds, and usages fields can be set on
    creation. Other fields are derived by Kubernetes and cannot be modified by
    users.

  status	<CertificateSigningRequestStatus>
    status contains information about whether the request is approved or denied,
    and the certificate issued by the signer, or the failure condition
    indicating signer failure.


