KIND:       ConfigMap
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    ConfigMap holds configuration data for pods to consume.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  binaryData	<map[string]string>
    BinaryData contains the binary data. Each key must consist of alphanumeric
    characters, '-', '_' or '.'. BinaryData can contain byte sequences that are
    not in the UTF-8 range. The keys stored in BinaryData must not overlap with
    the ones in the Data field, this is enforced during validation process.
    Using this field will require 1.10+ apiserver and kubelet.

  data	<map[string]string>
    Data contains the configuration data. Each key must consist of alphanumeric
    characters, '-', '_' or '.'. Values with non-UTF-8 byte sequences must use
    the BinaryData field. The keys stored in Data must not overlap with the keys
    in the BinaryData field, this is enforced during validation process.

  immutable	<boolean>
    Immutable, if set to true, ensures that data stored in the ConfigMap cannot
    be updated (only object metadata can be modified). If not set to true, the
    field can be modified at any time. Defaulted to nil.

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object's metadata. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata


