GROUP:      apps
KIND:       ControllerRevision
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    ControllerRevision implements an immutable snapshot of state data. Clients
    are responsible for serializing and deserializing the objects that contain
    their internal state. Once a ControllerRevision has been successfully
    created, it can not be updated. The API Server will fail validation of all
    requests that attempt to mutate the Data field. ControllerRevisions may,
    however, be deleted. Note that, due to its use by both the DaemonSet and
    StatefulSet controllers for update and rollback, this object is beta.
    However, it may be subject to name and representation changes in future
    releases, and clients should not depend on its stability. It is primarily
    for internal use by controllers.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  data	<RawExtension>
    Data is the serialized representation of the state.

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object's metadata. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata

  revision	<integer> -required-
    Revision indicates the revision of the state represented by Data.


