GROUP:      storage.k8s.io
KIND:       CSIDriver
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    CSIDriver captures information about a Container Storage Interface (CSI)
    volume driver deployed on the cluster. Kubernetes attach detach controller
    uses this object to determine whether attach is required. Kubelet uses this
    object to determine whether pod information needs to be passed on mount.
    CSIDriver objects are non-namespaced.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object metadata. metadata.Name indicates the name of the CSI driver
    that this object refers to; it MUST be the same name returned by the CSI
    GetPluginName() call for that driver. The driver name must be 63 characters
    or less, beginning and ending with an alphanumeric character ([a-z0-9A-Z])
    with dashes (-), dots (.), and alphanumerics between. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata

  spec	<CSIDriverSpec> -required-
    spec represents the specification of the CSI Driver.


