GROUP:      storage.k8s.io
KIND:       CSINode
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    CSINode holds information about all CSI drivers installed on a node. CSI
    drivers do not need to create the CSINode object directly. As long as they
    use the node-driver-registrar sidecar container, the kubelet will
    automatically populate the CSINode object for the CSI driver as part of
    kubelet plugin registration. CSINode has the same name as a node. If the
    object is missing, it means either there are no CSI Drivers available on the
    node, or the Kubelet version is low enough that it doesn't create this
    object. CSINode has an OwnerReference that points to the corresponding node
    object.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object's metadata. metadata.name must be the Kubernetes node name.

  spec	<CSINodeSpec> -required-
    spec is the specification of CSINode


