GROUP:      storage.k8s.io
KIND:       CSIStorageCapacity
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    CSIStorageCapacity stores the result of one CSI GetCapacity call. For a
    given StorageClass, this describes the available capacity in a particular
    topology segment.  This can be used when considering where to instantiate
    new PersistentVolumes.
    
    For example this can express things like: - StorageClass "standard" has
    "1234 GiB" available in "topology.kubernetes.io/zone=us-east1" -
    StorageClass "localssd" has "10 GiB" available in
    "kubernetes.io/hostname=knode-abc123"
    
    The following three cases all imply that no capacity is available for a
    certain combination: - no object exists with suitable topology and storage
    class name - such an object exists, but the capacity is unset - such an
    object exists, but the capacity is zero
    
    The producer of these objects can decide which approach is more suitable.
    
    They are consumed by the kube-scheduler when a CSI driver opts into
    capacity-aware scheduling with CSIDriverSpec.StorageCapacity. The scheduler
    compares the MaximumVolumeSize against the requested size of pending volumes
    to filter out unsuitable nodes. If MaximumVolumeSize is unset, it falls back
    to a comparison against the less precise Capacity. If that is also unset,
    the scheduler assumes that capacity is insufficient and tries some other
    node.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  capacity	<Quantity>
    capacity is the value reported by the CSI driver in its GetCapacityResponse
    for a GetCapacityRequest with topology and parameters that match the
    previous fields.
    
    The semantic is currently (CSI spec 1.2) defined as: The available capacity,
    in bytes, of the storage that can be used to provision volumes. If not set,
    that information is currently unavailable.

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  maximumVolumeSize	<Quantity>
    maximumVolumeSize is the value reported by the CSI driver in its
    GetCapacityResponse for a GetCapacityRequest with topology and parameters
    that match the previous fields.
    
    This is defined since CSI spec 1.4.0 as the largest size that may be used in
    a CreateVolumeRequest.capacity_range.required_bytes field to create a volume
    with the same parameters as those in GetCapacityRequest. The corresponding
    value in the Kubernetes API is ResourceRequirements.Requests in a volume
    claim.

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object's metadata. The name has no particular meaning. It must be a
    DNS subdomain (dots allowed, 253 characters). To ensure that there are no
    conflicts with other CSI drivers on the cluster, the recommendation is to
    use csisc-<uuid>, a generated name, or a reverse-domain name which ends with
    the unique CSI driver name.
    
    Objects are namespaced.
    
    More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata

  nodeTopology	<LabelSelector>
    nodeTopology defines which nodes have access to the storage for which
    capacity was reported. If not set, the storage is not accessible from any
    node in the cluster. If empty, the storage is accessible from all nodes.
    This field is immutable.

  storageClassName	<string> -required-
    storageClassName represents the name of the StorageClass that the reported
    capacity applies to. It must meet the same requirements as the name of a
    StorageClass object (non-empty, DNS subdomain). If that object no longer
    exists, the CSIStorageCapacity object is obsolete and should be removed by
    its creator. This field is immutable.


