GROUP:      discovery.k8s.io
KIND:       EndpointSlice
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    EndpointSlice represents a set of service endpoints. Most EndpointSlices are
    created by the EndpointSlice controller to represent the Pods selected by
    Service objects. For a given service there may be multiple EndpointSlice
    objects which must be joined to produce the full set of endpoints; you can
    find all of the slices for a given service by listing EndpointSlices in the
    service's namespace whose `kubernetes.io/service-name` label contains the
    service's name.
    
FIELDS:
  addressType	<string> -required-
  enum: FQDN, IPv4, IPv6
    addressType specifies the type of address carried by this EndpointSlice. All
    addresses in this slice must be the same type. This field is immutable after
    creation. The following address types are currently supported: * IPv4:
    Represents an IPv4 Address. * IPv6: Represents an IPv6 Address. * FQDN:
    Represents a Fully Qualified Domain Name. (Deprecated) The EndpointSlice
    controller only generates, and kube-proxy only processes, slices of
    addressType "IPv4" and "IPv6". No semantics are defined for the "FQDN" type.
    
    Possible enum values:
     - `"FQDN"` represents a FQDN.
     - `"IPv4"` represents an IPv4 Address.
     - `"IPv6"` represents an IPv6 Address.

  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  endpoints	<[]Endpoint> -required-
    endpoints is a list of unique endpoints in this slice. Each slice may
    include a maximum of 1000 endpoints.

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object's metadata.

  ports	<[]EndpointPort>
    ports specifies the list of network ports exposed by each endpoint in this
    slice. Each port must have a unique name. Each slice may include a maximum
    of 100 ports. Services always have at least 1 port, so EndpointSlices
    generated by the EndpointSlice controller will likewise always have at least
    1 port. EndpointSlices used for other purposes may have an empty ports list.


