KIND:       Event
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    Event is a report of an event somewhere in the cluster.  Events have a
    limited retention time and triggers and messages may evolve with time.
    Event consumers should not rely on the timing of an event with a given
    Reason reflecting a consistent underlying trigger, or the continued
    existence of events with that Reason.  Events should be treated as
    informative, best-effort, supplemental data.
    
FIELDS:
  action	<string>
    What action was taken/failed regarding to the Regarding object.

  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  count	<integer>
    The number of times this event has occurred.

  eventTime	<string>
    Time when this Event was first observed.

  firstTimestamp	<string>
    The time at which the event was first recorded. (Time of server receipt is
    in TypeMeta.)

  involvedObject	<ObjectReference> -required-
    The object that this event is about.

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  lastTimestamp	<string>
    The time at which the most recent occurrence of this event was recorded.

  message	<string>
    A human-readable description of the status of this operation.

  metadata	<ObjectMeta> -required-
    Standard object's metadata. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata

  reason	<string>
    This should be a short, machine understandable string that gives the reason
    for the transition into the object's current status.

  related	<ObjectReference>
    Optional secondary object for more complex actions.

  reportingComponent	<string>
    Name of the controller that emitted this Event, e.g.
    `kubernetes.io/kubelet`.

  reportingInstance	<string>
    ID of the controller instance, e.g. `kubelet-xyzf`.

  series	<EventSeries>
    Data about the Event series this event represents or nil if it's a singleton
    Event.

  source	<EventSource>
    The component reporting this event. Should be a short machine understandable
    string.

  type	<string>
    Type of this event (Normal, Warning), new types could be added in the future


