GROUP:      scheduling.k8s.io
KIND:       PriorityClass
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    PriorityClass defines mapping from a priority class name to the priority
    integer value. The value can be any valid integer.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  description	<string>
    description is an arbitrary string that usually provides guidelines on when
    this priority class should be used.

  globalDefault	<boolean>
    globalDefault specifies whether this PriorityClass should be considered as
    the default priority for pods that do not have any priority class. Only one
    PriorityClass can be marked as `globalDefault`. However, if more than one
    PriorityClasses exists with their `globalDefault` field set to true, the
    smallest value of such global default PriorityClasses will be used as the
    default priority.

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object's metadata. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata

  preemptionPolicy	<string>
  enum: Never, PreemptLowerPriority
    preemptionPolicy is the Policy for preempting pods with lower priority. One
    of Never, PreemptLowerPriority. Defaults to PreemptLowerPriority if unset.
    
    Possible enum values:
     - `"Never"` means that pod never preempts other pods with lower priority.
     - `"PreemptLowerPriority"` means that pod can preempt other pods with lower
    priority.

  value	<integer> -required-
    value represents the integer value of this priority class. This is the
    actual priority that pods receive when they have the name of this class in
    their pod spec.


