GROUP:      resource.k8s.io
KIND:       ResourceSlice
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    ResourceSlice represents one or more resources in a pool of similar
    resources, managed by a common driver. A pool may span more than one
    ResourceSlice, and exactly how many ResourceSlices comprise a pool is
    determined by the driver.
    
    At the moment, the only supported resources are devices with attributes and
    capacities. Each device in a given pool, regardless of how many
    ResourceSlices, must have a unique name. The ResourceSlice in which a device
    gets published may change over time. The unique identifier for a device is
    the tuple <driver name>, <pool name>, <device name>.
    
    Whenever a driver needs to update a pool, it increments the
    pool.Spec.Pool.Generation number and updates all ResourceSlices with that
    new number and new resource definitions. A consumer must only use
    ResourceSlices with the highest generation number and ignore all others.
    
    When allocating all resources in a pool matching certain criteria or when
    looking for the best solution among several different alternatives, a
    consumer should check the number of ResourceSlices in a pool (included in
    each ResourceSlice) to determine whether its view of a pool is complete and
    if not, should wait until the driver has completed updating the pool.
    
    For resources that are not local to a node, the node name is not set.
    Instead, the driver may use a node selector to specify where the devices are
    available.
    
    This is an alpha type and requires enabling the DynamicResourceAllocation
    feature gate.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object metadata

  spec	<ResourceSliceSpec> -required-
    Contains the information published by the driver.
    
    Changing the spec automatically increments the metadata.generation number.


