KIND:       Secret
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    Secret holds secret data of a certain type. The total bytes of the values in
    the Data field must be less than MaxSecretSize bytes.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  data	<map[string]string>
    Data contains the secret data. Each key must consist of alphanumeric
    characters, '-', '_' or '.'. The serialized form of the secret data is a
    base64 encoded string, representing the arbitrary (possibly non-string) data
    value here. Described in https://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc4648#section-4

  immutable	<boolean>
    Immutable, if set to true, ensures that data stored in the Secret cannot be
    updated (only object metadata can be modified). If not set to true, the
    field can be modified at any time. Defaulted to nil.

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object's metadata. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata

  stringData	<map[string]string>
    stringData allows specifying non-binary secret data in string form. It is
    provided as a write-only input field for convenience. All keys and values
    are merged into the data field on write, overwriting any existing values.
    The stringData field is never output when reading from the API.

  type	<string>
    Used to facilitate programmatic handling of secret data. More info:
    https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/configuration/secret/#secret-types


