GROUP:      authorization.k8s.io
KIND:       SelfSubjectRulesReview
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    SelfSubjectRulesReview enumerates the set of actions the current user can
    perform within a namespace. The returned list of actions may be incomplete
    depending on the server's authorization mode, and any errors experienced
    during the evaluation. SelfSubjectRulesReview should be used by UIs to
    show/hide actions, or to quickly let an end user reason about their
    permissions. It should NOT Be used by external systems to drive
    authorization decisions as this raises confused deputy, cache
    lifetime/revocation, and correctness concerns. SubjectAccessReview, and
    LocalAccessReview are the correct way to defer authorization decisions to
    the API server.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard list metadata. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata

  spec	<SelfSubjectRulesReviewSpec> -required-
    Spec holds information about the request being evaluated.

  status	<SubjectRulesReviewStatus>
    Status is filled in by the server and indicates the set of actions a user
    can perform.


