KIND:       ServiceAccount
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    ServiceAccount binds together: * a name, understood by users, and perhaps by
    peripheral systems, for an identity * a principal that can be authenticated
    and authorized * a set of secrets
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  automountServiceAccountToken	<boolean>
    AutomountServiceAccountToken indicates whether pods running as this service
    account should have an API token automatically mounted. Can be overridden at
    the pod level.

  imagePullSecrets	<[]LocalObjectReference>
    ImagePullSecrets is a list of references to secrets in the same namespace to
    use for pulling any images in pods that reference this ServiceAccount.
    ImagePullSecrets are distinct from Secrets because Secrets can be mounted in
    the pod, but ImagePullSecrets are only accessed by the kubelet. More info:
    https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/containers/images/#specifying-imagepullsecrets-on-a-pod

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object's metadata. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata

  secrets	<[]ObjectReference>
    Secrets is a list of the secrets in the same namespace that pods running
    using this ServiceAccount are allowed to use. Pods are only limited to this
    list if this service account has a "kubernetes.io/enforce-mountable-secrets"
    annotation set to "true". The "kubernetes.io/enforce-mountable-secrets"
    annotation is deprecated since v1.32. Prefer separate namespaces to isolate
    access to mounted secrets. This field should not be used to find
    auto-generated service account token secrets for use outside of pods.
    Instead, tokens can be requested directly using the TokenRequest API, or
    service account token secrets can be manually created. More info:
    https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/configuration/secret


