GROUP:      storage.k8s.io
KIND:       StorageClass
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    StorageClass describes the parameters for a class of storage for which
    PersistentVolumes can be dynamically provisioned.
    
    StorageClasses are non-namespaced; the name of the storage class according
    to etcd is in ObjectMeta.Name.
    
FIELDS:
  allowVolumeExpansion	<boolean>
    allowVolumeExpansion shows whether the storage class allow volume expand.

  allowedTopologies	<[]TopologySelectorTerm>
    allowedTopologies restrict the node topologies where volumes can be
    dynamically provisioned. Each volume plugin defines its own supported
    topology specifications. An empty TopologySelectorTerm list means there is
    no topology restriction. This field is only honored by servers that enable
    the VolumeScheduling feature.

  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object's metadata. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata

  mountOptions	<[]string>
    mountOptions controls the mountOptions for dynamically provisioned
    PersistentVolumes of this storage class. e.g. ["ro", "soft"]. Not validated
    - mount of the PVs will simply fail if one is invalid.

  parameters	<map[string]string>
    parameters holds the parameters for the provisioner that should create
    volumes of this storage class.

  provisioner	<string> -required-
    provisioner indicates the type of the provisioner.

  reclaimPolicy	<string>
  enum: Delete, Recycle, Retain
    reclaimPolicy controls the reclaimPolicy for dynamically provisioned
    PersistentVolumes of this storage class. Defaults to Delete.
    
    Possible enum values:
     - `"Delete"` means the volume will be deleted from Kubernetes on release
    from its claim. The volume plugin must support Deletion.
     - `"Recycle"` means the volume will be recycled back into the pool of
    unbound persistent volumes on release from its claim. The volume plugin must
    support Recycling.
     - `"Retain"` means the volume will be left in its current phase (Released)
    for manual reclamation by the administrator. The default policy is Retain.

  volumeBindingMode	<string>
  enum: Immediate, WaitForFirstConsumer
    volumeBindingMode indicates how PersistentVolumeClaims should be provisioned
    and bound.  When unset, VolumeBindingImmediate is used. This field is only
    honored by servers that enable the VolumeScheduling feature.
    
    Possible enum values:
     - `"Immediate"` indicates that PersistentVolumeClaims should be immediately
    provisioned and bound. This is the default mode.
     - `"WaitForFirstConsumer"` indicates that PersistentVolumeClaims should not
    be provisioned and bound until the first Pod is created that references the
    PeristentVolumeClaim. The volume provisioning and binding will occur during
    Pod scheduing.


