GROUP:      admissionregistration.k8s.io
KIND:       ValidatingAdmissionPolicyBinding
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    ValidatingAdmissionPolicyBinding binds the ValidatingAdmissionPolicy with
    paramerized resources. ValidatingAdmissionPolicyBinding and parameter CRDs
    together define how cluster administrators configure policies for clusters.
    
    For a given admission request, each binding will cause its policy to be
    evaluated N times, where N is 1 for policies/bindings that don't use params,
    otherwise N is the number of parameters selected by the binding.
    
    The CEL expressions of a policy must have a computed CEL cost below the
    maximum CEL budget. Each evaluation of the policy is given an independent
    CEL cost budget. Adding/removing policies, bindings, or params can not
    affect whether a given (policy, binding, param) combination is within its
    own CEL budget.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object metadata; More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata.

  spec	<ValidatingAdmissionPolicyBindingSpec>
    Specification of the desired behavior of the
    ValidatingAdmissionPolicyBinding.


