GROUP:      storage.k8s.io
KIND:       VolumeAttributesClass
VERSION:    v1

DESCRIPTION:
    VolumeAttributesClass represents a specification of mutable volume
    attributes defined by the CSI driver. The class can be specified during
    dynamic provisioning of PersistentVolumeClaims, and changed in the
    PersistentVolumeClaim spec after provisioning.
    
FIELDS:
  apiVersion	<string>
    APIVersion defines the versioned schema of this representation of an object.
    Servers should convert recognized schemas to the latest internal value, and
    may reject unrecognized values. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#resources

  driverName	<string> -required-
    Name of the CSI driver This field is immutable.

  kind	<string>
    Kind is a string value representing the REST resource this object
    represents. Servers may infer this from the endpoint the client submits
    requests to. Cannot be updated. In CamelCase. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#types-kinds

  metadata	<ObjectMeta>
    Standard object's metadata. More info:
    https://git.k8s.io/community/contributors/devel/sig-architecture/api-conventions.md#metadata

  parameters	<map[string]string>
    parameters hold volume attributes defined by the CSI driver. These values
    are opaque to the Kubernetes and are passed directly to the CSI driver. The
    underlying storage provider supports changing these attributes on an
    existing volume, however the parameters field itself is immutable. To invoke
    a volume update, a new VolumeAttributesClass should be created with new
    parameters, and the PersistentVolumeClaim should be updated to reference the
    new VolumeAttributesClass.
    
    This field is required and must contain at least one key/value pair. The
    keys cannot be empty, and the maximum number of parameters is 512, with a
    cumulative max size of 256K. If the CSI driver rejects invalid parameters,
    the target PersistentVolumeClaim will be set to an "Infeasible" state in the
    modifyVolumeStatus field.


